SIWAKRIT PATTAVEESIN

Email: mr.siwakrit@gmail.com

Phone: 091-035-7830

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/siwakrit-pattaveesin

GitHub: github.com/Siwakrit

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Completed Generation Thailand's Junior Software Developer Bootcamp (Cohort 8). With 1 year and 7 months of experience as an IT Project Coordinator (Chinese Skills Hsk5) and a 4-year degree in Education of Chinese Language from China, I have developed strong communication, teamwork, adaptability, management, and problem-solving skills. Proficient in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node.js, Express, relational databases, and MongoDB. Seeking a Software Developer position where I can contribute to a company that values achievement, motivation, and teamwork.

SKILLS AND ABLILITIES

- Technical skills: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, Node JS, Express, Relational databases, MongoDB
- Soft skills: Growth Mindset, Teamwork, Problem Solving, Communication, Adaptability, Management
- Language skills: English(intermediate), Chinese (HSK5)

EXPERIENCE

Junior Software Developer Bootcamp (Cohort 8)

Sep 2024 - Dec 2024

Generation Thailand

- Learned how to build web applications using React (front-end), Node.js (back-end), and MongoDB (database).
- Learned essential skills for switching careers, such as growth mindset, communication, and teamwork

Final Project: MERN Stack CRUD Project

- Ecommerce project with a team of 4 members, utilizing Scrum and Agile methodologies.
- Worked flexibly without fixed roles, allowing for role rotation and skill development.
- Divided tasks into three main sprints to meet Generation Thailand's requirements and ensure timely completion.
- Managed tasks and updates via Trello, emphasizing equal workload distribution and teamwork.

Landlink Consultant (Thailand) Co., Ltd.

Technical Operations (Chinese Skills Hsk5)

Job Description

- Responsible for the promotion and operation of the company's app and official website, formulating and implementing
 marketing plans based on company strategy.
- Developed promotional content for company products and utilize various marketing methods and channels to increase app downloads and website traffic.
- Analyzed company operational data and collaborated with technical staff to optimize products and content, maintain product
 performance and being accountable for key operational metrics such as user volume and activity levels.
- Established and managed the company's operational service system, addressing customer inquiries and facilitating customer transactions.

Global Jet Express (Thailand) Co., Ltd.

Sep 2022 - Mar 2024

Part-time: August 2024 - Present

IT Project Coordinator (Chinese Skills Hsk5)

Job Description

- Coordinated within organization. (Chinese and Thai Staff / Chinese headquarters)
- Responsible for IT system testing and provide feedback to develop the system operation.
- Handled all documents related to IT systems such as open or close Email application form, computer repair application form and so on.
- · Other work per assigned.

Project

• Installed servers at True IDC, processing purchase requests and coordinating as a Chinese interpreter between Thai IT support, Chinese developers, and external suppliers to ensure smooth installation and configuration.

EDUCATION

Huaqiao University (China)

Sep 2018 - Jun 2022

Bachelor of Education

Majoring in Education of Chinese Language